Severe Weather Update |Stay informed and safe. Visit our Severe Weather Updates page for more information on current conditions of Hurricane Milton and the latest updates.

Severe Weather Update |Stay informed and safe. Visit our Severe Weather Updates page for more information on current conditions of Hurricane Milton and the latest updates.

Severe Weather Update |Stay informed and safe. Visit our Severe Weather Updates page for more information on current conditions of Hurricane Milton and the latest updates.

Severe Weather Update |Stay informed and safe. Visit our Severe Weather Updates page for more information on current conditions of Hurricane Milton and the latest updates.

Severe Weather Update |Stay informed and safe. Visit our Severe Weather Updates page for more information on current conditions of Hurricane Milton and the latest updates.

Global Search Bar

Search _FAIRWINDS_ site and member support articles

Search

[Log In](https://www.fairwinds.org/login)Hamburger Menu Icon

Privacy Policy
==============

_FAIRWINDS_ Credit Union and its affiliates are committed to making available financial products and services that will enable you to meet your financial goals.

SVG Wave

### Your Personal Information

What does _FAIRWINDS_ Credit Union do with your personal information?

#### Why?

Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some, but not all, sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.

#### What?

The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:

* Social Security Number and Income
    
* Mortgage Rates/Payments
    
* Account Balances and Payment History
    
* Credit History and Credit Scores

When you are _no longer_ our member, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.

#### How?

ll financial companies need to share members' personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their members' personal information; the reasons _FAIRWINDS_ Credit Union chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.

### Reasons We Can Share Your Personal Information

|     | Does _FAIRWINDS_ share? | Can you limit this sharing? |
| --- | --- | --- |
| **For our everyday business purposes —** such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus | **Yes** | **No** |
| **For our marketing purposes —** to offer our products and services to you | **Yes** | **No** |
| **For joint marketing with other insurance/financial companies** | **Yes** | **No** |
| **For our affiliates' everyday business purposes —** information about your transactions and experiences | **Yes** | **No** |
| **For our affiliates' everyday business purposes —** information about your creditworthiness | **No** | **We don't share** |
| **For affiliates to market to you** | **Yes** | **Yes** |
| **For nonaffiliates to market to you** | **No** | **We don't share** |

### **To Limit Our Sharing**

Mail us a letter with "Do not allow your affiliates to use my personal information to market to me" and include your name, address, city, state, zip, and phone number.

#### Mail to:

_FAIRWINDS_ Credit Union Attn: Member Services 3087 N. Alafaya Trail Orlando, FL 32826

If you are a new member, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we sent this notice. When you are no longer our member, we continue to share your information as described in this notice. However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.

#### Questions?

Call 407.277.5045

### Who We Are

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **Who is providing this notice?** | _FAIRWINDS_ Credit Union |

### What We Do

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **How does** **_FAIRWINDS_** **Credit Union protect my personal information?** | To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings. |
| **How does** **_FAIRWINDS_** **Credit Union collect my personal information?** | We collect your personal information, for example, when you:<br><br>Open accounts or deposit money<br><br>Pay your bills or apply for a loan<br><br>Use your credit or debit card<br><br>We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies. |
| **Why can't I limit all sharing?** | Federal law gives you the right to limit only:<br><br>Sharing for affiliates' everyday business purposes—information about your creditworthiness<br><br>Affiliates from using your information to market to you<br><br>Sharing for non-affiliates to market to you<br><br>State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing. |
| **What happens when I limit sharing for an account I hold jointly with someone else?** | Your choices will apply to everyone on your account. |

### Definitions

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **Affiliates** | Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.<br><br>Our affiliates include financial companies with a "_FAIRWINDS_" name, such as _FAIRWINDS_ Insurance Services, LLC. |
| **Non-affiliates** | Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.<br><br>_FAIRWINDS_ Credit Union does not share information with non-affiliates so that they can market to you. |
| **Joint marketing** | A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.<br><br>Our joint marketing partners include insurance companies, credit monitoring companies, financial advisors, and securities brokers. |

Financial Freedom happens here.®

##### Company

##### Rates and Charges

##### Mobile Apps

##### Media

##### Connect with Us

Routing Number ⑆ 263181368

© 2024 _FAIRWINDS_ Credit Union
